Where to click on insurance reminder
and after that the link that comes here
[Music]
Renwal comes
now copy it from here i dot ICC
lombard.com/app and at last click 6x
double click it will open it will open
Chrome it will
auto open on Chrome browser
[Music]
update it click on bed
[Music] say yes otherwise say no
and you will do that then whoever is
asking for your previous policy, I have done
my previous policy from this company
[Music]
it is doing it,
this page will open the page of KYC process, send a
message on WhatsApp, it will
open, when it opens then
our KYC is done directly
[Music] if we make the
payment then the policy is there and it will be sent on
both mail and WhatsApp